# JAN **Doleček**

Soukenická 5 Brno. 608 00

**a** +420 774 178 554

≥ juzna.cz@qmail.com

www.juzna.cz

🐙 github.com/juzna

@juznacz

### PROFILE

Experienced software developer with knowledge of many programming languages, networking, Linux administration and theoretical informatics. Focused on web technologies, data processing, open source and security in IT.

Enjoys working in small teams on challenging projects, enthusiastic about learning new things.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Worked for both small and big companies, as a freelancer, contributor to open source projects.

2012 - PRESENT

### PeckaDesign

# PeckaDesign

Lead Developer

Development of web applications and E-shops; project analysis, team management.

2012

### Honeywell

### Honeywell

Master Thesis Intern at IT Support Analysis, design and implementation of Test related metrics.

2011



### eDigitalResearch

Data System Developer

Development of web-based research system Data processing and analysis.



N Inetrans

### 2006-2010

### Helemik

Internet Service Provider (ISP)

Web developer, system architect, leading programmer, network administrator.

### **SKILLS**

Experience with almost every programming language, database and development methodology.

PHP Deep knowledge of OOP and MVC, using every day.

Nette, Zend, Symfony, WebArchitekt.

JAVA Deep knowledge; Spring, EJB, jUnit.

DATABASES Deep knowledge of SQL and document databases

and ORM; MySQL, PostgreSQL and MongoDB.

JAVASCRIPT Deep knowledge of OOP, AJAX, building rich UI.

Using every day; jQuery, Prototype.

C, C++ Intermediate knowledge, using where speed is priority.

RUBY Basic knowledge.

PROLOG Intermediate knowledge, using for fast prototyping.

VCS Git, Subversion.

# 2002-2006

### Inetrans

Web agency, CRM, E-shops

Lead developer.

# EDUCATION

Always reaching the top, love exploring new topics. Learning theory but focusing on real life.



### 2007-2013

### Masaryk University, BSc + MSc Applied Informatics

Prestige Czech University

In top 5% of students doing the same course.
Focus on networking - wireless networks,
network applications and security.
Experience in team work, requirements analysis,
application design. Received several grants for

application design. Received several grants for projects on data-mining for University.

University of **Portsmouth** 

### 2010-2011

### University of Portsmouth, BSc Computing

Prestige UK University

Exchange student - one semester.

Focus on web technologies and networking. Gained experience in English, working in teams and giving presentations.

### LANGUAGES

Enthusiastic to learn foreign languages.

CZECH Native speaker

ENGLISH C1 - fluent in spoken and written, 1 year in UK GERMAN B1 - intermediate, 8 years at grammar school

SPANISH A2 - beginner, 2 years at grammar school

### HOBBIES

My work is my hobby. I love experimenting and startups. When not on the PC, I dive into maths or theoretical informatics. Relaxing in gym, swimming pool, running or cycling. Love driving my car.